{
    "subject": "resource/Alexandra_Orlando",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthDate",
    "object": "1987-01-19",
    "human_readable": "Alexandra Orlando was born on January 19, 1987.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8866018056869507,
            "question": "When was Alexandra Orlando born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8584734797477722,
            "question": "January 19th of which year marks Alexandra Orlando's birthday?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7589511871337891,
            "question": "What is Alexandra Orlando's birthdate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6632286906242371,
            "question": "What month and day was Alexandra Orlando born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6142266988754272,
            "question": "How old is Alexandra Orlando?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6041303277015686,
            "question": "What day of the week was Alexandra Orlando born on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5588683485984802,
            "question": "Is Alexandra Orlando's birthdate in the winter or summer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5019629001617432,
            "question": "Alexandra Orlando's birthdate falls in what season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40092334151268005,
            "question": "In what year did Alexandra Orlando come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30267319083213806,
            "question": "If today is October 26th, 2023, how many days have passed since Alexandra Orlando's birth?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Alexandra Orlando was born on January 19, 1987.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3382_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did Alexandra Orlando come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3382_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Alexandra Orlando's birthdate falls in what season?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3382_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Alexandra Orlando's birthdate in the winter or summer?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3382_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3382_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3382_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3382_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3382_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3382_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3382_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3382_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3382_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3382_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3382_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The first document mentions Alexandra Orlando's early life and background, stating that she was born on January 19, 1987. This directly confirms the triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide the birth date of Alexandra Orlando as January 19, 1987. Therefore, the statement \"Alexandra Orlando was born on January 19, 1987\" is supported by the given context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}